Guide to the New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Development and Alumni Affairs records, 1960-1995.
New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Development and Alumni Affairs records, 1960-1995
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Development and Alumni Affairs records, 1960-1995.
21-2-1767
New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Development and Alumni Affairs
2.4 cubic ft.
Minutes, correspondence, audiocassettes
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records of the Cornell College of Agriculture's Development and Alumni Affairs office include correspondence, proposals, minutes, reports, donor lists, accounts, date books, and other materials relating to corporate and alumni gifts, scholarships, the College of Agriculture and Life Sciences Fund, and other subjects. Names included are Laing E. Kennedy, A. Lee Thompson, William I. Myers, Lansing P. Shield, W. Keith Kennedy, A. Bradford Carruth, Wendell G. Earle, and Elmer L. Townsend. Includes photographs and slides of various events and people, such as David Call and of campus buildings, including the demolition of Roberts Hall in 1990.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records of the Cornell College of Agriculture's Development and Alumni Affairs office include correspondence, proposals, minutes, reports, donor lists, accounts, date books, and other materials relating to corporate and alumni gifts, scholarships, the College of Agriculture and Life Sciences Fund, and other subjects. Names included are Laing E. Kennedy, A. Lee Thompson, William I. Myers, Lansing P. Shield, W. Keith Kennedy, A. Bradford Carruth, Wendell G. Earle, and Elmer L. Townsend. Includes photographs and slides of various events and people, such as David Call and of campus buildings, including the demolition of Roberts Hall in 1990.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Call, David L., 1932-; Carruth, A. Bradford.; Earle, Wendell, 1923-; Kennedy, Laing E.; Kennedy, W. Keith, 1919-; Myers, William Irving, 1891-1976.; Shield, Lansing P.; Thompson, A. Lee.; Townsend, Elmer L.; Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae.; Cornell University--Buildings; Roberts Hall (New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences).; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Alumni and alumnae.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Endowments.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Funds and scholarships..; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Finance.
Subjects:
Educational fund raising.; Slides (photographs).; Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- College of Agriculture Fund - Financial Needs of Students, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- College of Agriculture - Alumni Association and Fund, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Summary of Gifts, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- College of Agriculture Fund - List of Pledges - Upstate, NY, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Inquiry Letters and Responses, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Lansing P. Shield Memorial Scholarship Fund, July 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Sears-Roebuck Foundation Scholarship, 1960-1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Summary of Gifts, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Letters sent to Dairy Farmers, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Ag Fund - Hudson Valley, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Scholarships and Awards, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Request for Permanent Operation of Fund, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- College of Agriculture and Life Science Council Meeting, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Fund Advisory Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Foundation Gifts to Cornell, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Corporate Gifts, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Fund Summary, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Fund Reports, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Faculty Response, March 1973 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Laing Kennedy Date Book, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Cornell Fund for College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Scholarships and Awards, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Treasurer's Book, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- A. Lee Thompson, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Advisory Committee Agenda, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Donor's List, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Conferences, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Gifts and Programs, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Action for a Creative Fund, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Proposals and Projects, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Faculty Response to Letter, Feb. 1974 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Donor Lists, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Annual Report Brochure, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Fund Committees, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Elmer T. Townsend Proposal, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Fund, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Summary of Endowed Accounts, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Projects and Proposals, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Services, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Standing Committees, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Annual Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Permanent Operation of the Fund, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Laing Kennedy Date Book, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Donor List, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- General CALS Fund, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Laing Kennedy Date Book, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Payroll Deductions, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Private Grants, Contracts, and Gifts, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Charter and Tower Gifts, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Committee Meeting, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Progress Report, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Proposals and Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Laing Kennedy Date Book, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Memo Book Bradford Carruth, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, Jan. 1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, Feb. and Mar. 1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, Apr. and May 1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, Jun. and Jul. 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, Aug. and Sep. 1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, Oct., Nov., and Dec. 1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Bradford Carruth Memo Book, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Bradford Carruth Memo Book, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- William I. Myers Professorship Solicitation Letters, Apr. 1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- William I. Myers Papers, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- William I. Myers Prospects, Action, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- William I. Myers Professorship, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Requests for Pledges to William I. Myers Professorship, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- William I. Myers Professorship Correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- William I. Myers Professorship Booklets (Box 3, Folder 6b)
- Wendell G. Earle Testimonial Dinner Correspondence, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Wendell G. Earle Testimonial Dinner Menu, Programs, Photograph, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Chinese Agricultural Education Delegation - photograph and flyer, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- David Atkinson '60 - Foremost Benefactors Ceremony - photos, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- David Call - Reviewing Plans for New Roberts Hall - slides, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- David Call's Portrait Unveiling (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Dr. Austin Curtis Jr. '32 - 60th Reunion - photos and clippings, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Wendell G. Earle - photos (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Dean Beverly Galloway's Portrait - CALS Alumni Assocation Meeting - photos, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Keith Kennedy - photos and slides (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Lee Teng-hui - photos and program, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Dean Daryl Lund with composite picture of campus - photo, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Ronald Lunch Deanship Dedication - photos and program, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Isaac Roberts, Dean - photo (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Eloy Rodriquez - slides, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Agriculture Quad Tree Planting - slides and flyer, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Akwe:kon House Dedication - slides, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Alpha Zeta Fraternity Dedication with Frank Rhodes - slides, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Campus Buildings - photos (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Campus Buildings - slides (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Campus Buildings - slides (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Campus Buildings - slides (Box 3, Folder 28)
- "Herakles at Ithaca" Dedication - Jason Seley - photos (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Roberts Hall Demolition - slides, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Roberts Hall Demolition - photos, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Old Roberts Hall Brick Presentation with Dean Call - slides (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Stone Microcomputer Center Dedication Ceremony - photos, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 33)